Contact

hello@isaque.me

isaque.me (Portfolio)
isaque.me/linkedin (Linkedin)

Top Skills

Brand, Creative, & Pd Strategy
Product & Service Ideation
Stats & Psychometrics
Digital Design · Filmmaking · Public Speaking
R · SPSS · HTML/CSS · Marketing Strategy

Languages

English (Native/Bilingual)
Portuguese (Native/Bilingual)
Spanish (Full Proficiency)
Hungarian (Elementary)
Dutch (Elementary)

Honors & Awards

2022 Global Cannes Young Lions Thronze (Digital)

2022 Young Lions NL Y Gold (Fairphone)

2022 Young Lions NL ▼ Silver (Mentelity Found.)

2022 Young Lions NL ▼ Honors (Buma X YouTube)

2021 Young Lions NL ** Bronze (Concertgebouw)

Amsterdam Mobility Challenge

★ Silver (ADE)

FACAMP Web Game

* National Champion

2022 LIA Creative Liaisons ♠ Mentee

Passports

Brazilian Italian

ISAQUE SENEDA

BRAND & PRODUCT STRATEGIST

Amsterdam, Netherlands

Summary

I am a strategist with product ideation, brand, and consumer research skills. Brazilian w/ 4 countries & counting.

I create products that tell stories because products are stories (Berkeley, 1713). In it to fix real problems.

Fluent in behavioral sciences, psychometrics, and stats.

Holland Code

→ #「 ~~> ~@

Entrepreneurial • Artistic • Investigative

CliftonStrengths

Competition • Significance • Restorative • Communication • Focus

Experience

PUBLICIS ITALY / LE PUB

Creative & Product Strategist
Jun 2021 - Present (1 year 6 months)
Amsterdam, Netherlands

Here I had the opportunity to join the global Heineken team alongside top talent from the ad industry. After Data Lab, I now work at Le Garage (product/tech team) as a creative strategist using data to ideate innovation-led campaigns.

WINEPOPPER

Brand & Product Strategist Jan 2021 - Dec 2021 (1 year) São Paulo, Brazil

I kickstarted the process of positioning and rebranding of Winepopper (a Brazilian gas wine opener) as a "magic kit for 40+ wine lovers". The process involved managing market research, art direction, product design, and media buying.

MUSEU DO AMANHÃ (MOTI)

Digital Designer & Brand Strategist Nov 2018 - Jun 2021 (2 years 7 months) Amsterdam, Netherlands

In this traineeship alongside school, I headed the development of FORMS' global brand identity both in terms of brand strategy, as well as digital design. FORMS is collaborative platform connecting sustainability museums worldwide.

Education

ROTTERDAM SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT, ERASMUS UNIVERSITY

MSc, Marketing Management · (2020 - 2021)

PARSONS SCHOOL OF DESIGN, THE NEW SCHOOL

Study Abroad, Communication Design · (2020 - 2020)

UNIVERSITY OF AMSTERDAM

BSc, Communication Science (▼Honors) · (2017 - 2020)
Minor, Business Administration · (2018 - 2019)

ESCOLA SUPERIOR DE PROPAGANDA E MARKETING

Portfolio School, Arenas ESPM · (2016 - 2016)

WILLEM DE KOONING ACADEMY

Propedeuse, Audiovisual Design · (2016 - 2017)

Volunteer Experience

ROTARY INTERNATIONAL

Youth Exchange Student in Hungary Aug 2014 - Jul 2015 (1 year)

UNIVERSITY OF AMSTERDAM

MEGA TABLE, Founder & Stats Tutor Oct 2017 - Present (4 years 10 months)